Vikram Pandit

vkpandit.herokuapp.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Leetcode

Location: Jivdani Heights, Narangi Phata, Virar - 401305 Email: vkpandit1909@gmail.com | Mobile: 8208230693

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I am a highly skilled full stack developer with over 2 years of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, WordPress, and PHP. I have knowledge of popular frameworks such as React, jQuery, and Node.js and experience with REST APIs and MVC frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : Python, JavaScript, PHP, HTML, CSS

: React.js, Express, Node.js **Frameworks** Frameworks-App: Flutter, React Native, Cordova

Databases : MongoDB, SQL

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, Gitlab, Github

EXPERIENCE

System Associate

Pune, Maharashtra, India Infosys Ltd

Created multiple VM instances of Windows Server 2012 R2 using Hyper-V to work on Active Directory Domain

- Configured Windows Server Administration by creating DNS routing(Forward and Reverse Lookup Zones) along with **DHCP** Installation
- Worked with SCCM to make Software Centre available for the devices in the given domain and then make software available according to the requirement
- Created a few PowerShell scripts to automate the process

Junior Developer

Jul 2020 - Aug 2021

Oct 2022 - Present

Illustrake

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

- Worked with React Native and Cordova to develop robust and scalable applications compatible for multiple platforms
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases
- Troubleshot and fixed bugs and issues in the backend to ensure smooth operation of the applications

Web Developer Intern

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

Creative Pills Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

- Assisted senior web developers in the design and development of websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- · Created a few websites using WordPress, PHP, and JavaScript

Software Developer Intern

3GRT Interactive

Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

- Assisted senior app developers in the design and development of applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with the help of **Cordova** framework
- Created multiple SQL queries required for the development of the applications

EDUCATION

Viva College

University of Mumbai

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India June 2019 - May 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India June 2017 - May 2019

Higher Secondary Certificate (Computer Science)

Phasor

JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, Website Hosting and Domain Transfer

- Designed and developed a clean and modern website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Optimized website for speed and user experience
- Utilized **responsive design** to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Deployed on Bluehost and transferred the domain from the previous hosting provider to the current one.

Janki Jewellery

React.js, Node.js, Express, JavaScript, Git

- Designed and developed a clean, modern, and responsive eCommerce website along with an admin dashboard panel using **React.JS**, **Material UI**, **and Bootstrap**
- A **CRUD application** exposed using a RESTful API made with Node.js
- Exposed POST, GET, PATCH, and DELETE HTTP methods using Express

Haati

React Native, Fabric.js, JavaScript, Git

- Designed and developed a robust and scalable application using **React Native**
- Implemented Fabric.js in order to achieve the main customization functionality in the application

KFZapp

Flutter, PHP, Gitlab

- Designed and developed a clean, and modern application along with an admin dashboard panel using Flutter,
 Bootstrap, and PHP
- A CRUD application exposed using a RESTful API made with PHP
- · Manage and Maintain the server based on Linux Ubuntu

CERTIFICATIONS

- Participation Certificate by Skillyst Techtopia (Coding Challenge)
- Bootstrap Certificate by Finolex Academy of Management and Technology
- Python Completion Certificate by IIT Bombay